Financial Statement [of the University] UP070
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Financial Statement [of the University]
1921 -- 1995
1880 -- 2001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Executive Vice President
UP070
2.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the published financial statements of Tufts University, published by the Office of the Executive Vice President, from 1880 to 2001.
- Financial statement [of the University], 1880 -- 2001; UP070.001; 2.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the published financial statement of Tufts University.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged as found.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Financial Statements, 1966 -- 1978; UP070.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1981 -- 1985; UP070.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1986 -- 1987; UP070.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1987 -- 1988; UP070.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1989 -- 1991; UP070.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1991 -- 1995; UP070.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1995 -- 1996; UP070.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1997; UP070.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Annual financial report of Tufts University, 2001; UP070.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1921 -- 1925; UP070.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1925 -- 1929; UP070.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1929 -- 1933; UP070.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1933 -- 1936; UP070.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1936 -- 1940; UP070.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1940 -- 1944; UP070.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1944 -- 1947; UP070.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1947 -- 1950; UP070.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1950 -- 1952; UP070.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1952 -- 1954; UP070.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1954 -- 1956; UP070.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1956 -- 1960; UP070.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1880 -- 1884; UP070.001.008.00001 (Box 8)